<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Austin&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>https://austinj1522.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Austin&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:43:57 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://austinj1522.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Setting up a Domain</title>
      <link>https://austinj1522.github.io/blogs/customdomain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:43:57 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://austinj1522.github.io/blogs/customdomain/</guid>
      <description>A Step-by-step Guide to Custom Domains with Github To add a custom domain to your newly created website, the process is fairly simply. For this process, I&amp;rsquo;ll be referring to the same project discussed in my previous post that is this website which is hosted via Github Pages.&#xA;Step 1 - Purchase Domain The first step of this process is going to be to purchase your preferred domain via a domain provider.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About this Website!</title>
      <link>https://austinj1522.github.io/blogs/website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 00:43:57 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://austinj1522.github.io/blogs/website/</guid>
      <description>How I built this website, and how you can too! Hey, thanks for checking out this post. This will be a quick read on how I host and maintain this website! Keep in mind, this post is written with the assumption that you are familiar with programming languages, version control, and some HTML/Markdown experience. To get started, you&#39;ll need a github account, and the following software installed: git GO programming language Hugo Depending on what operating system you are using, you may need to install the software differently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://austinj1522.github.io/blogs/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 00:43:57 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://austinj1522.github.io/blogs/first/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my personal website!&#x9;This is my personal website! Feel free to browse to view my education, background, and professional experience. You can also see some of my personal projects and certifications I have taken, or plan on taking in the near future. My next post will explain how I built this website, and what skills were required to do so. Subsequent posts will explain projects I am actively engaged in, so stick around to find out more!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
